Brothers,
الإخوة،
the thief Cheng Dalei
اللص تشنغ دالي
did harm to the City Owner.
أضر بمالك المدينة.
He has a deep blood feud with me in Black Rock City.
لديه عداء عميق معي في بلاك روك سيتي.
I will kill him.
سأقتله.
Revenge.
انتقام.
Let's do
دعنا نفعل
Lu Hum now.
لو هم الآن.
Lu Hum,
لو هوم
I didn't kill the City Owner of Han.
أنا لم أقتل صاحب مدينة هان.
Don't be fooled by Xue Banchuan.
لا تنخدع Xue Banchuan.
He colluded with the Rong Clan,
لقد تواطأ مع Rong Clan ،
and harmed City Owner Han.
وألحق الضرر بمالك المدينة هان.
But evil dog thief,
لكن لص الكلب الشرير ،
kill the City Owner first,
اقتل مالك المدينة أولاً ،
Now,
الآن،
you still dare to use counter-tactics to provoke the relationship
ما زلت تجرؤ على استخدام التكتيكات المضادة لإثارة العلاقة
between me and the Military Advisor,
بيني وبين المستشار العسكري ،
I'll kill you now.
سأقتلك الآن.
Hyah!
Hyah!
Master, you're still smart.
سيدي ، ما زلت ذكيًا.
Ask Shaoyu to change into your clothes and lure the army away.
اطلب من Shaoyu تغيير ملابسك وإغراء الجيش بعيدًا.
Let's go back.
دعنا نعود.
Stealing Xue Banchuan's Tiger Tally.
سرقة تالي نمر Xue Banchuan.
Which way should we go, Advisor?
أي طريق يجب أن نسير أيها المستشار؟
I've seen the stars,
رأيت النجوم
Greed goes west,
يذهب الجشع غربًا ،
Misfortune
مصيبة
leads to the east. This way.
يؤدي إلى الشرق.  من هنا.
Okay,
تمام،
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Stop!
قف!
Who are you?
من أنت؟
Hold on.
يتمسك.
These two are my guests.
هذان هما ضيوفي.
Why did you rush into the city?
لماذا هرعت إلى المدينة؟
If they find out,
إذا اكتشفوا ،
it will cause trouble, won't it?
سوف يسبب المتاعب ، أليس كذلك؟
Why aren't you talking?
لماذا لا تتكلم
It's good that
من الجيد ذلك
you're alert enough.
أنت متيقظ بما فيه الكفاية.
Let the prince rest assured that
دع الأمير يطمئن إلى ذلك
I have the Tiger Tally,
لدي Tiger Tally ،
We can dispatch troops to take you
يمكننا إرسال قوات لأخذك
into the prison by midnight tonight.
في السجن بحلول منتصف الليل.
When I take down Dawu State and become the emperor,
عندما أسقط ولاية داو وأصبحت إمبراطورًا ،
the land of Youbei.
ارض اليوبي.
It will be yours
سيكون لك
until then,
حتى ذلك الوقت،
I hold the power
أنا أمتلك القوة
and look down on the world.
وينظر إلى العالم بازدراء.
Come on.
تعال.
When I think about it carefully,
عندما أفكر في الأمر بعناية ،
Cheng Dalei
تشنغ دالي
is quite capable.
قادر تمامًا.
Yes.
نعم.
If we keep this person,
إذا احتفظنا بهذا الشخص ،
it will be a big trouble.
ستكون مشكلة كبيرة.
not be as good as
لا تكون جيدة مثل
We'll exterminate Toad Village tonight.
سنبيد قرية العلجوم الليلة.
Kill him clean.
اقتله نظيفا.
It doesn't matter.
لا يهم.
I'll be right back.
سأعود حالا.
Bro,
أخ،
which door should we go out faster?
أي باب يجب أن نخرج أسرع؟
That way.
من ذلك الطريق.
What kind of person?
أي نوع من الأشخاص؟
Lu Hum, it's me.
لو هوم ، هذا أنا.
I didn't expect you to throw yourself into the net.
لم أكن أتوقع منك أن تلقي بنفسك في الشباك.
Today is the day you die.
اليوم هو يوم موتك.
It's just a small trick.
إنها مجرد خدعة صغيرة.
You're dying,
أنت تحتضر
yet you want to stab someone in the back?
ومع ذلك تريد طعن شخص ما في ظهره؟
What's that?
ما هذا؟
Tiger Tally?
تايجر تالي؟
Keep it safe.
حافظ على سلامته.
If it falls into Xue Banchuan's hands,
إذا وقع في يد Xue Banchuan ،
the State of Great Wu will be wiped out.
سيتم القضاء على دولة وو العظمى.
At midnight,
في منتصف الليل،
Xue Banchuan will open the city gate to lure the Rong Clan to invade,
سيفتح Xue Banchuan بوابة المدينة لجذب Rong Clan للغزو ،
Why should I believe you?
لما يجب علي تصديقك؟
I dare not forget to worry about the country,
لا أجرؤ على أن أنسى القلق على البلد ،
how can I drive Lu to ask about cloth and silks.
كيف يمكنني أن أقود لو أسأل عن القماش والحرير.
How do you know that?
كيف تعرف ذلك؟
Did you see those two men in black?
هل رأيت هذين الرجلين يرتديان ملابس سوداء؟
Those two distinguished guests?
هذين الضيفين الكرام؟
I showed them the way.
أريتهم الطريق.
They even praised me for being great.
حتى أنهم أشادوا بي لكوني رائعًا.
Go and get them back.
اذهب واسترجعهم.
Okay, okay.
حسنا حسنا.
It's God's will.
انها مشيئة الله.
General,
عام،
Xue Banchuan has escaped from the city.
هرب Xue Banchuan من المدينة.
Lu,
لو ،
you go and regroup the troops,
تذهب وتعيد تجميع القوات ،
I'll go after Xue Banchuan.
سأذهب بعد Xue Banchuan.